# **Hunt Hung**

UIUX / Product Designer Web-Fn-Developer

#### INTRO

I'm a product designer that crafts digital experiences to empower people. I have 5 years of related experience in the field covering not only designer's role but also as web front-end developer and team lead.

I am capable of performing a variety of skills including visualisation, user testing, fn-coding, video editing and 3d rendering.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# MANTRA DAO - UIUX Designer (Contract)

Jun 2021 - present

Responsible for auditing the company existing UI performance. Study the feedback from the community users and make instant adjustments. Set priority and practical deployment schedules with dev-team. Suggesting better workflow, housekeeping tools as well as rebuilding a scalable design system.

# Oursky - Product Designer

Nov 2018 - Mar 2021 (2 yrs and 5 mnths)

Responsible for clarifying clients' needs, drafting userflow, crafting UI and UIQA. User research including surveying and A/B testing is occasionally a must. Experience in various types of contracts from MVP, POC, waterfall to agile. Internal housekeeping in providing peer feedback as well as self-retro sharing.

# Firmstudio — Web Designer & Fn-Developer

Jan - Sep 2018

Responsible for a wide range of job contents ranging from graphic design to web fn-development. Act as a bridge between design and development team to tackle difficulties encountered during design-to-fn transition.

## Creasant — Web Designer & Design Lead

Sep 2016 - Nov 2017

Responsible for UI design of the company's web projects. Visualise clients' brief in a pracable manner. Partnered with the development team to cope with design constraints and make instant modifications. Present to the client on ideas generated and explain if there are any practical concerns with solutions provided. Acquiring and supervising new hires after being promoted.

#### **PORTFOLIO**

hlh112.github.io/portfo

#### CONTACT

mobile +852 93061692

+46 72-945 64 83

email hunter252006@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

/ Design Thinking

/ Lean UX

/ User Research

/ Wireframing

/ Prototyping

/ User Testing

/ Visual Design

/ 3D Rendering

/ Motion Graphic

/ Photo Retouching

/ HTML/SCSS/JS

/ SEO

## **INDUSTRIES COVERED**

Crypto DeFi Construction Industry eCommerce Event Management

Al-powered Apps Online Rental
Sports Social Platform

#### **TOOLS**

Figma Marvel App
Sketch Maze Design
Adobe XD Webflow
Photoshop Zeplin
Illustrator Overflow
InDesign Lottie
AfterEffect Blender 3D

Invision

#### **EDUCATION**

# Hong Kong Polytechic University

BA (Hons) Design – Visual Communication

2012 - 2016